http://www.gijoepriceguide.com/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
Your Privacy
Your privacy is important. To better protect your privacy, this policy is provided explaining this website's online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve advertisements to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google's own privacy policies.
Collection of Personal Information
When visiting GIJoePriceGuide.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links to Third Party Websites
Links are included on this site for your use and reference. This website is not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from this one.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at my discretion.
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of GIJoePriceGuide.com, then you may contact me.
How do I fix that?
Joe Lingo
Other GI Joe Sites
Contact
© 2006-2020 GIJoePriceGuide.com. Privacy Policy. Valid CSS & XHTML. Template design by Arcsin
